<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic on Pan Feng</title>
    <link>panfeng0119.github.io/tags/academic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academic on Pan Feng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="panfeng0119.github.io/tags/academic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>panfeng0119.github.io/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>panfeng0119.github.io/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. Check out the latest demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the Quick Start guide or take a look at the Release Notes.

Key features:
 Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Extensible via color themes and widgets/plugins Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Multilingual and easy to customize  Color Themes Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Page Resources</title>
      <link>panfeng0119.github.io/post/pagesource/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>panfeng0119.github.io/post/pagesource/</guid>
      <description>CONTENT MANAGEMENT
Page Resources ResourceType The main type of the resource. For example, a file of MIME type image/jpg has for ResourceType image. Name Default value is the filename (relative to the owning page). Can be set in front matter. Title Default blank. Can be set in front matter. Permalink The absolute URL to the resource. Resources of type page will have no value. RelPermalink The relative URL to the resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>将 Hugo 站点托管在 GitHub</title>
      <link>panfeng0119.github.io/post/%E6%89%98%E7%AE%A1%E5%9C%A8github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>panfeng0119.github.io/post/%E6%89%98%E7%AE%A1%E5%9C%A8github/</guid>
      <description>完整内容请参阅 Hosting &amp;amp; Deployment. 我们可以将 Hugo 生成的站点托管在 GitHub Pages 上，并使用简单的shell脚本自动完成整个过程。假设您已完成： 已安装 Git 版本 2.8 以上. 在 GitHub 中</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>